i was gonna say hello but it looks like
these guys have done it for me
hello my name is green and welcome back
to hermitcraft six i have been hunting
phantoms but i legit have been like
dreaming about them i had a dream that
cub fan had like 2 000 kills and i gave
up in a fit of rage but honestly the
time is coming up very soon for this
contest to end i've got three days three
days oh mumbo jumbo says my redstone is
working well that's new to me uh the cup
fan has two
1270 phantom kills i have 776
and with three days left i don't see it
happening so i don't know whether to
waste time at all i think he's got a big
enough lead that it's out of my reach
oh my goodness look at this this looks
awesome does this mean i have mail oh my
goodness okay so
if i put an item in here it goes green
and if i take the item out
it goes back to normal oh that's
brilliant let's check that the redstone
is working on mumbo side as well
that definitely looks like it's working
i've got a brilliant idea
i'm hoping that this works because i
think this could be really funny
if if i could spawn chickens yep i hear
them spawning
[Laughter]
poultry man strikes again oh that's
totally clogging it's totally clogging
up the system with chickens
they're not moving at all
i probably should have i should have
checked this before
wait are they moving oh my goodness
they're actually
they're moving they're slowly going i
reckon if we let them do their thing
they'll eventually just move into the
water and make their way to mumbo's base
we should check if it actually like gets
an item stuck in there as well just in
case we are clogging up the system with
chickens i love how mumbo's just
finished all this and i'm immediately
just breaking it by filling it with
chickens looks like the items just pass
on through and while we're at it why
don't we rename a few of these eggs
poultry man strikes again and throw them
in as well
just throw them in as items and then
fill them up with some chickens as well
they may the great thing about this is
that these chickens might take a really
really long time to make their way
through the system if they get stuck on
the ice and they like don't actually
just walk around
this could be like a really long-term
investment of just chickens popping
through the woodwork
okay so i've added some additions here
as well for mumbo to enjoy i've got
poultry man is definitely not green
poultry man strikes again and i'll leave
the rest for you guys to read on mumbo's
video and they go
and in they go yep we've got okay yeah
we've got
trident dude
where is he
where is he i could see i could see the
trident coming through but i don't see
him oh wait yeah
oh i got him nailed him we should go and
see if we got a trident from him i
should have used my looting sword
no way
no way did he drop a trident
oh my goodness
that is so rare this didn't go exactly
to plan because as you can see
the chickens are they're just sitting in
the air pockets
not doing anything
but it seems like they are getting
somewhere this guy's in the lead oh my
goodness we should take bets on who's
gonna go to get to mumbo's base first
this could take a seriously long time
for them to get there
but
it could be really funny this could be
like a really long term thing i think
i'm gonna unload the rest of these eggs
into the system i am slightly in love
with this idea and it looks like
someone's left me a message as well how
did i not notice this
green oh the reaper requests your
presence in the shopping district
now
well when was this left alright let's
just get rid of these chickens first
i'm sure the reaper can wait
all right let's head over to the
shopping district then
okay so what exactly am i looking for
my presence is required here
hello
ah
well if that isn't the grim reaper i
don't know what is now i've never
encountered zf before so this is yeah
this is a new encounter let's see if we
can go and say hello
all right
how's it going oh my goodness
what is are you okay
i'm fine i've never been better but are
you okay is the question
yeah
is that what i mean i've never talked to
you before is this what you normally
sound like because it's kind of scary
is it scary i thought it sounded kind of
cool
what what's going on with your skin why
are you all
like armored up this is this is my robes
this is my usual my usual nightwear
so
did you leave me the message because
it's only between you and cub fan
it was me i am the reaper
okay
i am dead
well i to be honest with you i don't
really need i don't need any more death
i die enough in in this series as it is
to be
well my honest might be right down your
alley then
okay
um where is your challenge
it's right here
in the pickle shop
well just out
just out front okay all right lead the
way then i i don't know why i'm
following you but go go ahead i'll take
your challenge
do you want to know what the challenge
is no no no no no no no no no no no soon
as i tell you the time will start oh for
real
we do it right here
okay
all right go ahead go ahead i'm ready
i'm ready
get to zero health as quickly as you can
go
come on
no i didn't go fast enough
i don't know why i'm following your
instructions
beautiful
this pleases me greatly
what do i win
uh i don't know yet
what
i haven't got that far ahead what do you
mean
um well yeah
i've challenged the other hands too and
it's whatever gets so you might have
lost
ah
if i had known what the challenge was i
would become better prepared
well hey
death is always prepared i imagine that
everyone's gonna go for the same tactic
they might remember to take their armor
off first
oh
yeah i'm not the best at this
you pleased me greatly though watching
you splat on the floor was it's made my
night
i'm now gonna retreat
back to the underworld and i'll reveal
whether you're the winner or not soon
well i def i definitely am not but
thanks i guess
you're welcome
bye-bye
bye
and here's iska now in order to
combat cubs insane
phantom lead what i'm doing is enlisting
the help of everyone that wants to see
cub fail this task and i'm getting them
to afk here
and i'm making booths for everyone
there we go
and now everyone has a booth see we've
got red and dog here we've got
uh oh how do you say how do you say his
name um
z
z zoo z z zumu so everyone now has their
own little booths as you can see i've
put them on the island here and they all
have access to the sky so they've all
got like a gap here
and that means that
if they looked up they'd see the sky
meaning that the phantoms will spawn and
i assure them their safety as i will be
the protector but i also think that when
it turns day i'm gonna go and get a few
iron golems just in case to protect and
walk around i don't want anything bad
happening to my team here the theory is
that these guys will all spawn their own
phantoms in along with mine making it
possible for me to kill four times as
many phantoms as i normally would and
the date is closing in i'm on 785 and
cub is well over a thousand two hundred
so
i've really got a lot of catching up to
do
this should be a lot of fun but i also
i'm also waiting quite a lot so
i gotta kind of keep myself busy i guess
which is why i thought it'd be funny to
make sure that we
give
give them the treatment that they
deserve excise zuma do not feed
oh my goodness that's a lot oh oh no no
no no
oh no no no bad timing bad timing bad
timing i need to get into the air if i
want to grab these ones
i can get them
okay there's one last one
yes
that was a lot okay so now that these
guys are consistently spawning phantoms
i'm able to
up my limit quite a lot so i actually
killed 11 that night but i actually only
killed two the night before so i'm
hoping when these guys haven't slipped a
lot they're going to be spawning in
phantoms just as much as me
oh thank goodness it's day for a bit
though because now i can leave these
guys to be
so he is ishgal he's swede
it the light has turned green
let's see what's going on here
one egg one egg did mumbo send me back
just one egg i can still i could still
see chickens in there now wait a minute
did he actually send me an egg or hold
on i think i might know what's going on
here
there's still some chickens in there's
still chickens all in the system but i
have a feeling i know what's happened
i think the chicken bomb thing
seems to have worked oh
yeah
this is exactly what i was hoping for
oh that that's how i'm ending up with
eggs
there are chickens in his send pile
laying eggs and that's how i'm getting
all this mail so that'll end that'll end
up back in my mail room so any moment
now
the mail should pop out of here
there it is
straight in
and then this should go green
that is absolutely brilliant i'm loving
this system i really am it's good fun
now to protect my bros who are helping
me out
let's enlist the help of some golems
which i never really do oh i got there
you go i've got hired help so just in
case something nasty spawns around these
guys
will help
could you imagine if they spawned but
the head was just there oh dear
and we got wendog he a cool dude he is a
really cool dude actually and now we
just gotta wait for another night ah the
sun is going down it's starting to get
really really dangerous now it's i think
the phantoms are finally spawning for
everyone because these
are spawning by the bucket load in just
tonight the one night after i was
complaining it's now
839. they are spawning in so much i've
turned on hitboxes so that i can see
where i need to actually hit because
with the phantom they've got quite an
odd and like long and thin hitbox so it
just makes it easier to be able to make
sure i bop them on the head that looks
like it for another night at hunting now
if i just get a few more nights like
that i'll catch up in no time but in the
meantime i'm going to be working on a
little secret
project well i have been grinding for
over seven hours now like legitimately
seven hours i've had different people
sit in afk but
it's time to pack up shop now i spent
all day well every minecraft night i was
killing phantoms and every minecraft day
i was working on the secret room over
there which we all know about it's
nearly finished but i don't know exactly
when it's going to be
in the next video i don't know i don't
know when it's actually going to appear
on your screen
but yeah it's time to just pack up and
call it quits because unfortunately
despite seven hours of grinding with six
afk people in total usually only three
at one time
cub fan still has one thousand three
hundred and seventy whereas i only
managed to get one thousand 1203
so this is me officially throwing in my
hat i give up i tried wasted a lot of
time but it was quite a lot of fun at
the same time i'm definitely better at
killing phantoms
and you can tell just how many phantom
heads and phantom membranes that i've
got but i think it's official because
this is what i'm going to do to throw in
my hat officially
i'm going to do what i haven't done in
many days
which is sleep and it even says a player
doesn't want anyone to sleep no it's
it's i'm gonna continue there we go i've
officially
thrown in the towel i don't want to see
another phantom for a very very long
time and i've also got more mail i have
been sending stuff to mumbo oh he just
there's just more eggs more eggs go you
know let's just keep sending them
i just realized that this is an
infinitely perpetuating prank because
the more chickens i throw down the chute
the more chickens that get stuck over in
mumbo's base the more eggs that come
through the system and the more eggs
i've chucked down the tube is a proper
circle of chickens poultry man strikes
again i'm gonna have to stop at some
point in other news i had to make my
spoiler wall
even bigger you can see look it properly
takes up all this space oh you can see a
bit there
let's just cover that up and i also have
added in an architect logo or what i
think could be a potential architect
logo it doesn't look quite as good as
i'd hoped
the a frame itself is too wide i would
prefer if it went sort of more
longer i guess but
i think this looks pretty cool it's got
like the over and it's got a little dash
here maybe i can make that a bit smaller
i don't know i quite like it i doesn't
have a t in it anywhere but it does have
a big a and then just a little bit of
decor i'll see what mumbo thinks to it
but i think starting to put together all
of this or architect logos and stuff is
a good idea as we're starting to do a
lot more projects now but you know the
phantom thing isn't the only competition
that's going on now i may have failed
the phantom thing but
this competition is called to kill a
tango and the idea is you have to come
up with the most creative way to kill
tango now you have to make a redstone
machine but i want to participate and i
don't do redstone so i thought i'd come
up with a pretty funny way to
but basically it's a joke submission i i
don't seriously think that this is going
to work but hopefully this should get a
really good laugh
it all hinges
on a big obsidian box
and i realize i'm going to need
way more obsidian
the idea is that i'm going to create an
infinity room for tango
and well i think we'll save how this is
actually going to go down and how this
might actually kill him for when we do
that segment when we actually record it
it will all make sense but for now i
need to make a little bit of a custom
infinity room just for him this should
bamboozle him just enough for me to get
away with what i plan on doing
but you may be wondering why this is
made out of obsidian well i won't keep
that one from you the reason is i don't
want him to escape it's quite simple but
he cannot escape oh my goodness i think
i just have enough for this
i do i literally just have enough it's
only going to be two blocks high he
won't be able to jump
but
this should do i might need to make it
one lower but let's see what this looks
like i've got loads of item frames and
maps i've actually stolen them from the
other infinity room but the back room so
the first room isn't completely ruined
and this may be tango's first look into
the infinity room so this could be a
really cool experience for him you know
i don't think i'll ever get used to this
and how weird it is
oh has mumbo sent me legit mail or is it
there's more there's a lot of eggs
oh my goodness
i know i keep getting distracted by this
but
this is hilarious i'm gonna have to stop
at some point because he's gonna shut
down the mail system and get really
annoyed but
okay just this episode just this one
episode poultry man strikes again okay
after this this will be the end of the
eggs all right because otherwise we're
just constantly gonna have mail
all right i must remember where this is
so open
and then all i gotta do is pop that oh
boy
as long as
i can i
i could jump
i can jump through here
maybe tango will do that but oh my
goodness
oh no i can't get out can i
i just did oh and there's phantoms no
i've had enough of you enough i don't
want it i'm done with this no more
no more
all right so the actual room that we're
gonna use is finished that's the main
thing
and hopefully if i just leave that it
could look like a little bit of a
surprise
that does look cool actually let's leave
it like that
and what we're going to do is create a
bit of a platform we're going to make a
real show out of this entire thing now i
have to admit what i have planned
does not follow the rules at all not one
bit like i'm probably going to be
disqualified straight away
so what i'm going to get him to do is oh
do you know what i could make like a
hangman thing
that could be really cool that looks
pretty good so we've got like a
hangman's thing here and all he's got to
do is press the button ah i might want
to turn that around so if he's standing
here
and he's got to
he's got to do his thing he's on he's on
death's row he presses this he falls
straight in and he's died he has he has
officially he's officially died he's
he's got oh no how do i get out of here
the trapdoor shut again
oh no
oh i did not think this through i did
not think this through at all
okay thank goodness for that we're gonna
open this
pop that down back and we can make it
out because we did it before
oh okay i got out oh that was
frustrating
okay
this is actually really difficult to get
out of now remember tango's not gonna
have any items on him that's very very
important he's not gonna have a single
item on him meaning that's why the
obsidian's here he will have to punch
his way out and i don't know if any of
you have ever had to punch obsidian out
with your hands in minecraft but
yeah you don't want to do that it takes
like 36
minutes
36 minutes so this is it this is
basically what i want to do with tango
and it should be a lot of fun very very
simple but
didn't take too long
i tell you what if i win this
competition just because it's going to
be funny i i will share the reward with
the person that actually did deserve to
win
mumbo is afk again
but where
oh mumbo okay i was gonna say he's not
very safe in there but he's pretty safe
for now
poultry man is back
look at his little face
look at his face
he's he's gonna come back and he's gonna
be he's gonna know exactly what's
happened here
but i know for a fact that he's not
there because it is relatively late at
night right now so he's definitely not
in his studio
so this is the perfect time to strike
at least when he gets to the other side
he's gonna have a really nice amount of
food
because all of these chickens are gonna
be ready to go
it wasn't me i swear officer it was the
man in the chicken costume
and now
my disguise is over
success
so the reason i've been putting off
building the outside of my base yes it's
still not done it's one because i've
been working on my project dirt house
but also because
i'm not sure and it is definitely time
to
do something with these towers here i
need to detail them in some way because
i don't want to leave them absolutely
clean
but at the same time they do look really
really nice but something's not quite
right and so i've asked for a copy of
the map and we're gonna go and
experiment with that so let's head over
to that world and take a quick look i
think we've had quite enough shenanigans
for this episode
it feels weird being in creative mode in
the hermitcraft server but of course i'm
not on the hermitcraft server at all i
am on my own private server taking a
look at my own base so i can experiment
with it before i commit to all of the
changes that i want to do so
i've been having a few ideas one is
adding a few more steps
and that might look right it might look
incredibly wrong i think we should try
that out first
the best thing about this is i have
welded it so i can do these sorts of
things incredibly fast
i think that's kind of made a difference
i'm not entirely sure
again this hasn't really helped me that
much it does make it more clean
but i'm pretty sure it's not quite right
especially the one at the top it feels
like it's off a few blocks do i risk
changing it and making it all different
or do i keep what i've got and stick
with it hmm i do think this looks a lot
cleaner though and i could even take it
one step further by making it even more
complicated if i added in just another
layer here to make it even more smooth
and sort of had this stop halfway
between the two it could seem like a
really smooth transition or it could
look like a mess
um i'm not sure about that one i think
we should keep it on the bigger side
with all of these steps so do we prefer
the bigger
steps that are more angular or do we
prefer the smoother ones that go down
and make it almost have a curve
not entirely sure at the moment but
whatever i choose to do it's going to
take a lot of work and time one thing is
for sure i want to knock back a block
and put in a bit of a detail here where
there is grey concrete behind what i'm
doing here so there's like
little notches that are
going down diagonally and i'm gonna do a
few lines of those and see what that
looks like
now taking a step back
that actually looks really good it
doesn't look good on its own but i think
with that replicated on every single
side
that's a really cool way to detail this
and it adds that extra element in there
i do really really like that it's now
about what else we can add to this to
make it look even better because i feel
like there's something missing from this
part majorly what if i had the same
thing going the other way
hmm
i'm not entirely sure but i think this
is on the right tracks i'm more inclined
to keep this detail on this tower but
again i'm not entirely sure these
experiments have been useful though it's
good to do it in creative instead of
committing in case
this doesn't work out please please
please let me know in the comments down
below what you think i should do and if
you have any more ideas
i'd like to hear your inputs before i go
any further so anyway thank you very
much for watching everyone this has been
a fantastic episode full of shenanigans
and progress and all kinds of weird
things thank you very much for watching
and good
bye